American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5001 PAM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 4, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: International Industrial Relations Congress, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: The Fourth Seminar in Mexico, 1929; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Questionaire sur les Aspects Sociaux de La Rationalisation, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: China Famine Relief, 1929; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: 5th International Medical Congress for Industrial Accidents and Occupational Diseases, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: L'Avenir Du Travail, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: Proposed international regulations and conventions, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 12: International Association for Social Progress, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Author: K. Von Blarer
  - Item 13: Program of the Annual Meeting, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 14: Minutes of General Meeting, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 15: Addendum to Constitution; Statement of Indifferences Between the Former Constitution and the New One Adopted at the Cambridge Meetings, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 16: Circulaire No. 24, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 17: Rapport du Secretaire General au Comite Directur de l'A.I.P.S., 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 18: Summary of the Conference on Fundamental Human Relationships in Industry held in Cambridge, England, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Author: Mary Van Kleeck
  - Item 19: Monthly Summary of the International Labour Organisation, 1929; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 20: Minimum Budget of Income and Expenditure, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Box: 4, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Circulaire n 47, 1933; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Author: A. Boissard
  - Item 2: Engberg v. Debel, et al No. 30274, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: A Short Summary of the Proposed Unemployment Insurance Law of Ohio, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Information Service, 1932; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Unemployment Insurance in Great Britain, 1930; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: 1931 World Social Economic Congress, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Circulaire No. 38, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Rapport du Secretaire General sur L'Activite de l'A.I.P.S, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: Compte du Semestre Financier ler Janvier - 30 Juin 1931 Halbjahresrechnung, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: Resolutions adoptes par la IV Assemblee generale des delegues (Paris 19-22 Octobre 1931), Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Language: Catalan.
  - Item 11: Memorandum on Election of Officers and Council Members, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Author: E. Brenda Voysey
  - Item 12: 60th Annual Meeting, American Public Health Association, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 13: Memorandum, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 14: Agenda for General Meeting of Members, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 15: Agenda for General Meeting of Members, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 16: Circulaire n 36, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 17: The Seminar in Mexico, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 18: The Seminar in Mexico Sixth Annual Session, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 19: Circulaire n 41, 1932; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 20: Circulaire n 46, 1933; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 21: Circulaire n 52, 1934; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 22: Circulaire N 55, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 23: Stabilization of Industry, 1931; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Author: Gerald Swope
- Box: 4, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: What the International Labor Office May Mean To American Labor, 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Legal Recognition of the worker's right to organize in the U.S.A., 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Summary of Proceedings, 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Bulletin of the International Federation of Trade Unions, 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Labor Laws of the United States of America, 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Author: Louis B. Wehle
  - Item 6: Questionnaire Concernant la Revision des Statuts de l'A.I.P.S., 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Box: 4, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: A Survey of Seven Years of Experimentation by Acts, Authorities and Administrations, 1940; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Labor Trends and Social Welfare in Latin America: 1939-1940, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Wartme Wages Policy, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Factory Inspection in Great Britain; Annual Report 1940, 1943; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: British Labor and the War, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Author: Frieda Wunderlich
  - Item 6: Labour Under German Democracy Arbitration 1918-1933, 1940; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Box: 5, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Sit-Down Strike, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Joel Seidman
  - Item 2: The Seamen's Right to Strike, 1942; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Louis Bloch
  - Item 3: A Detailed Review of the Coal Strike, 1917; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Facts Submitted by the Consumers' League of New York City, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Daily Consular and Trade Reports, 1912-1913 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: A Joint Resolution Directing the Secretary of State to Refer to the People for their Approval or Rejection A Profound Amendemtn to Section 7, Article 23 of the Constitution of Oklahoma and Calling A Special Thereon, 1941; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Injunction Against T. & N.O. Railroad Made Permanent, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The Use of Injunctions in Labor Disputes, 1929; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The Use of Injunctions in Labor Disputes, 1928; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: General Strike of the Ladies' Tailors, Custom Dressmakers, Theatrical Costume and Alteration Workers' Union, Local #38, International Ladies Garment Workers' Union, September 25, 1930, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Employment Agencies, 1928; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Instructions to Fill Out the Employer Schedule (Form UI-RS-8), 1940; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: fritz Kaufmann
  - Item 13: News Matter -- Rush, 1919; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Labor in the Peace Treaty, 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Box: 5, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Bills Acted Upon By Committee on Legislation Session of 1925, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Progress of Labor Legislation, 1925; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: Henry R. Seager
  - Item 3: Excerpt from the Department Report of the Investigation as to Causes for Existing Unemployment and Remedics therefor., 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Legislative Technique, 1933; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: Audrey M. Hayden
  - Item 5: Rules of the House of Representatives, 1929; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: House of Representatives Committee of Labor Thursday, February 20, 1930, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: William F. Kopp
  - Item 7: Progress Report of Legislative Committee American Vocational Association, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Deputy Commissioners Appointed Under the Longshoremen's and Harbor Workers' Compensation Act, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Fees Required to Accompany Applications for Entry, Reentry, or Additional entry of Publications as Second-Class Matter, 1932; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Industrial Homework Act; Suggested Language, 1934; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Minutes of Meeting of the Committee on Pending Social Legislation, held June 4, 1929, at 5 P.M., Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: World Almanac 1929 Questionnaire, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Exemptions from Tax on Corporations, 1932; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: State of Minnesota, vs. Walter A. Pocock, 1925; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: Grace F. Kaercher
  - Item 15: Chapter 530, 1929; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Memoranda on the Histoy of a Bill Declaring "Yellow Dog Contracts Null and Void, 1925; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Labor to Make Big Drive for Laws to Limit Equity Courts to Field of Property Rights, 1925; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: Chester M. Wright
  - Item 18: Minutes of Conference on Proposed Amendments to the Longshoremen's Act, 1928; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Abstracts of the Provisions of Anti Injunction Bill, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Box: 5, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Legislative Activity (Memo #2), 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Merrill G. Murray
  - Item 2: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: M. G. Murray
  - Item 7: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Merrill G Murray
  - Item 8: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Labor Legislation, 1935; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Association Acts On Pending Security Bills, 1935; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Unemployment Compensation, 1936; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Legislative Activity, 1937; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Social Security Board Administrative Order No. 3, 1936; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Legislation Relating to Labor Disputes, 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Box: 5, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Industrial Disputes; Speech of Charles Sumner Bird, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Charles Sumner Bird
  - Item 2: Extract from Report of A.F. of L. Executive Council, 1913; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: State of Conneticut, General Assembly, January Session A.D. 1913, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Conference to Consider Proposed Factory Legislation, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: State of Connecticut. General Asembly, January Session, A.D. 1913, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Journal of the House, 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Amendments - In Senate, 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Health Insurance, 1919; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Colorado, 1917; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Resolved: Senate Introductory 496, 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: A. M. Rosenthal
  - Item 13: Resolutions Adopted, 1915; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: In Assembly - Action on Assembly Bills, 1919; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Memorandum To All Department Heads, Branch Offices and Fieldmen; Workmen's Compensation Act, 1931; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: P. E. Pemberton
  - Item 16: Legislature Drafting, 1916; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Ernst Freund
  - Item 17: The Next Steps for Wisconsin; A Program of Construction, 1919; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: 21 CCA, 1923; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Report of the Nominating Committee, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Adelbert Moot
  - Item 20: Notice To Members; Reports of Nominating and Program Committees, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Meeting 3/15/1922 Zion Lutherian Church, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Decision on Annual Agreement, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Julian K. Mack
  - Item 23: Report of Status of Industrial Rehabilitation May 2, 1921, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: A Bill; extending the benefits of workmen's compensation to inlcude occupational diseases., 1921; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Mr. Wenner
  - Item 25: Extracts from Eighth Annual Report of the Department of Labor, 1924-1925, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Official Reporters of the Senate and Assembly, 1919, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: Proposed Constitutional Amendments, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Re Federation of Labor health Insurance Bill., 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: Provisions of Labor Law and Industrial Code, 1935; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: A Commission on Industrial Relations, 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Laws, Rules and Regulations, 1915; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Investigation of Needs of Nation for Public Works to Be Carried on in Periods of Business Depression and Unemployment, 1923; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: The Conference of Progressives, Preliminary Report of Proceedings, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Basil M. Manly
- Box: 5, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Draft of a Model Statute for Facilitating Enforcement of Wage Claims, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Reginald Heber Smith, Esq.
  - Item 2: Message of David Sholtz, 1933; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: David Sholtz
  - Item 3: Outline of Proposed Legislation to Facilitate Adjustment of Labor Dispute in Public Utilities, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Ship Subsidy Bill Digest of Facts and Arguments, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Charlotte A. Hankin
  - Item 5: A Description of the Association and a Statement of its Aims, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Memorandum - Corporate Connections of Harlan F. Stone, Through the Law Firms With Which He Is Connected, 1924; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Live and Publicity Report from January Third to April Eighteenth; Legislature Work, 1919; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Leading Progressives Tell Why the People's Lobby, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: John Dewey
  - Item 9: The Provisions of the Bill (Meyer-Ullman Bill), 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Objections to the Proposed Substitute Amendment No. 1. S to Bill 222 S, 1915; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Proponents of Social Legislation, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: John M. Thompson
  - Item 12: Resume of Bills Prepared by General Wyman and now before commmittee in the House of Representatives and the Senate, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: General Wyman
  - Item 13: Extracts from Letters Received at the Office of the Committee of One Hundred in Regard to General Wyman's Bills, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: The United Neighborhood House representing 60 settlements in New York City endorse the principle of unemployment reserves and are in favor of this bill, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Correction:, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Legislative Office, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: To the Officers and Members of the Allied Printing Trades Unions of New York State, 1922; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Peter J. Brady
  - Item 18: Synopsis, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: A.J. Pillsbury
  - Item 19: Notations by Sylvia Sachtjen, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Sylvia Sachtjen
  - Item 20: Would Throttle Private Initiative in favor of Unionism and Paternalism, 1928; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: State of New Jersey Department of State, 1932; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Thomas A. Mathis
  - Item 22: A Code of Standard Practices in the Administration of Workmen's Compensation Laws, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: Legislative Campaigns of the Playground and Recreation Association of America, 1918; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: Repeal of Prohibition Clause in State Constitution, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 25: Laws Administered by the Department of Labor, 1883-1912 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 26: Physical Exams; Indiana Legislature S.B. 159 (Lee), Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 27: Industry, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 28: Legislative Information, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 29: Some Questions Answered as to the Sullivan-Brooks Bill, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 30: Hewitt Legislation and Efficiency in Government, 1808; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Thomas I. Parkinson
  - Item 31: Special Bulletin; Railroad Propoganda, 1920; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 32: Material Relating to the Ship Subsidy Bill, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 33: Officers of the American Association for Agricultural Legislation, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 34: Classification of Certain employees in the U.S. Bureau of Animal Industry, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 35: Application for Membership in the American Association for Agricultural Legislation, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Box: 5, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Editorial Supplement to L & S Press Ervice, 1935; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Author: Paul Porter
  - Item 2: Proposal for Organiizing Collective Bargaining Associates, 1940; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Round Table, 1939; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Amer. Foundries v. Tri-City Council, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Box: 5, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Effective Merit Rating (Provisions and Administration) under state Unemployment Compensation Laws, 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Author: George F. Kull
- Box: 5, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: What we Are Doing For the Interstate Migrant, 1939; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Author: Carey McWilliams
  - Item 2: Congress Should Enact a Statute Regulating Interstate Labor Contractors, 1941; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Author: John H. Tolan
- Box: 5, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Can the Athracite Mine Workers Win a Strike?, 1911-1912 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Third Annual Report of State Mine Inspector, 1921; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: John Hanwell
  - Item 3: A Federal Minig Commission Address by John Randolph Haynes, M.D., 1912; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: John Randolph Haynes, M.D.
  - Item 4: Report of the Committee on Standardization of Mining Laws of the Mine Inspectors Institute of America, 1924; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Practical Application and Cost of Proper Rock-Dusting, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: G.M. Kintz
  - Item 6: Descroptive List of Motion-Picture Films and Plan of Sidtribution, 1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Fourteenth Annual Report of The State Inspector of Coal Mines to the Governor of New Mexico, 1925; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: pour la lutte contre la tuberculose; Programme et Reglement General, 1911; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Fifth National Standardization Conference, Mining Standards, 1924; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Aims and Activities, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Minutes Finance Committee, Monday, Dec. 5, 1910., Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Statistics for Producing Enterprises, By States 1919, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Proposed By-Laws of The Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1927; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Membership List District 25, 1923; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Membership List, 1923; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Table Showing Days Worked Number of Tons Shipped and Total Production for Each Mine in the State for the Year 1925, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: Agenda for Meeting Wednesday November 11, 1925., Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: Minutes Executive Committee Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1925; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Personnel of Sectional Committee on Safety Code for Coal Mine Transportation, 1925; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: Minutes Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1926; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 21: Coal Mine Safety- A Modern Challenge to the Mine Owner and Executive, 1927; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 22: Minutes Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1928; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 23: Minutes of Meeting of M S C C, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: P. G. Agnew
  - Item 24: Objects, 1931; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 25: Minutes of Meeting M S C C, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 26: Personnel of Sectional Committee on Safety Rules for Installed and Using Electrical Equipment in Metal Mines, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 27: Minutes Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1931; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 28: Minutes Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1932; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 29: Resolution, 1932; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: Byron O. Pickard
  - Item 30: Section 511, 1932; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 31: Minutes of the Organization Meeting of Sectional Committee for Specifications for Clean Bituminous Coal - M26, 1932; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Box: 5, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Decision of the Bituminois Coal Labot Board Division 2 in the Complaint Against the White Ash Coal Compant, Wheatland, Indiana, 1934; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Decision of the Bituminous Coal Labor Board, Division 2, in the Matter of the Hours per day and the days per Week for Hoisting Engineers, 1934; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Annual Meeting of American Institute of Mining and Mettalurgical Engineers Engineering Societies Building, 1934; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Bureau of Mines Committee Activities, 1934; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Minutes Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1935; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Minutes Standards Council, 1935; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Mining Standardization Correlating Committee, 1935; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)